headsetoptions.org 2016-03-15

# Wireless Broadband Internet from Blue Fire Broadband

* * *

Blue Fire Broadband is committed to ensuring your privacy. Any data you provide us, you can be sure, is secure and we will always respect your privacy. This is our responsibility to you and we take it seriously.

### Regarding Security

We have multiple procedures in place to insure that our servers and any data you provide us are 100% secure always. Chief among these is we hire third party, leading internet security firms to audit our privacy protection performance and to improve upon it. One of these vendors is VeriSign. If you provide us your personal information, you can be sure that is secure because any sensitive financial information will be collected on a Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Verisign SSL Certificates provide protection over your private data and e-commerce transactions you engage in while on our site. We also guarantee that all personal information is protected against unauthorized access. 

### Sharing of Private Information

Please know that first and foremost we will never sell your private information or share it unless compelled by state or federal law. We only collect your personal information when you register voluntarily here on our website. It is our policy to always maintain 100% user confidentiality. If you do sign up for WildBlue or Exede Satellite Internet service, it is mandatory for us to share your information with ViaSat (parent company of WildBlue and Exede) to complete your order. This same policy also applies if you contact us to initiate a service request. You can find WildBlue's privacy policy at wildblue.com and Exede's privacy policy at Exede.com. From time-to-time we may provide your contact information with select companies who we have an affiliate relationship with, in so that they may contact you regarding their products, offers and relevant services. In such a case, to maintain the privacy of your personal data, we will always require these companies to obey all tenants of our Privacy Policy and should you receive any correspondence from them, you will always have the right to opt-out from receiving any future communications from them. If you have previously registed with us and would like to cease receiving communications from us - or if you wish to update your personal information that we have on file from you - please get in touch with us using the Contact Information below.

### Cookie Usage Policy

In order to provide you with a more user-friendly and personalized website experience, Blue Fire Broadband may, at times, use digital files known as cookies to store and sometimes track your personal surfing habits and personal information while on our site only. This small cookie file is stored on your computer or laptop's hard drive. 

### Third party Advertising and Analytics

Blue Fire Broadband also reserves the right to utilize third-party analytics or advertising firms and/or software to provide ads on our behalf or to help us determine content that is more relevant for our users. We may also use these firms and/or software to provide performance metrics for our advertising efforts and to measure our website effectiveness. 100% of the information collected by these systems and efforts is completely anonymous.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

Blue Fire Broadband reserves the right to alter their privacy policy. Any alterations/changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted here on this website page.
